todo.ly 2010-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Todo.ly

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Todo.ly we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Todo.ly collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Todo.ly’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Todo.ly’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Todo.ly may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Todo.ly also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Todo.ly does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

When you register with Todo.ly we ask for information such as your name, email address and password. Your password will be maintained on our system in an encrypted form. For Todo.ly Premium we also store your PayPal email. Your information is only used internally and won't shared with other organizations.

Task list contents and usage. The contents of your Todo.ly account are stored and maintained on Todo.ly servers in order to provide the service. Because we keep back-up copies of data for the purposes of recovery from errors or system failure, residual copies of task list contents may remain on our systems for some time, even after you have deleted information or after the termination of your account. Todo.ly employees do not access the content of any task lists unless you specifically request them to do so (for example, if you are having technical difficulties accessing your account) or if required by law, to maintain our system, or to protect Todo.ly or the public. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

Todo.ly may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, Todo.ly does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Todo.ly discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Todo.ly’s behalf or to provide services available at Todo.ly’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. S ome of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Todo.ly’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Todo.ly will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Todo.ly discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Todo.ly believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Todo.ly, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Todo.ly website and have supplied your email address, Todo.ly may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Todo.ly and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Todo.ly takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Todo.ly uses cookies to help Todo.ly identify and track visitors, their usage of Todo.ly website, and their website access preferences. Todo.ly visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Todo.ly’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Todo.ly’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Todo.ly may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Todo.ly’s sole discretion. Todo.ly encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a wordpress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
